Finding Aid for the John J. Bonica Papers Biomed.0118
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Publications
  - Management of Pain, 2nd edition
    - General. Chapter 39. Illustrations [photocopies, captions, slides]. (Box 95, Folder 40)
    - General. Chapter 40. Illustrations [photocopies, captions, slides]. (Box 95, Folder 41)
    - General. Chapter 41. Illustrations [photocopies, captions, slides]. (Box 95, Folder 42)
    - General. Chapter 42. Illustrations [photocopies, captions, slides]. (Box 95, Folder 43)
    - General. Chapter 43. Illustrations [photocopies, captions, slides]. (Box 95, Folder 44)
    - General. Chapter 45. Illustrations [photocopies, captions, slides]. (Box 95, Folder 45)
    - General. Chapter 46. Illustrations [photocopies, captions, slides]. (Box 95, Folder 46)
    - General. Chapter 47. Illustrations [photocopies, captions, slides]. (Box 95, Folder 47)
    - General. Chapter 48. Illustrations [photocopies, captions, slides]. (Box 95, Folder 48)
    - General. Chapter 49. Illustrations [photocopies, captions, slides]. (Box 95, Folder 49)
    - General. Chapter 50. Illustrations [photocopies, captions, slides]. (Box 95, Folder 50)
    - General. Chapter 51. Illustrations [photocopies, captions, slides]. (Box 95, Folder 51)
    - General. Chapter 52. Illustrations [photocopies, captions, slides]. (Box 95, Folder 52)
    - General. Chapter 53. Illustrations [photocopies, captions, slides]. (Box 95, Folder 53)
    - General. Chapter 54. Illustrations [photocopies, captions, slides]. (Box 95, Folder 54)
    - General. Chapter 55. Illustrations [photocopies, captions, slides]. (Box 95, Folder 55)
    - General. Chapter 56. Illustrations [photocopies, captions, slides]. (Box 95, Folder 56)
    - General. Chapter 57. Illustrations [photocopies, captions, slides]. (Box 95, Folder 57)
    - General. Chapter 58. Illustrations [photocopies, captions, slides]. (Box 95, Folder 58)
    - General. Chapter 59. Illustrations [photocopies, captions, slides]. (Box 95, Folder 59)
    - General. Chapter 60. Illustrations [photocopies, captions, slides]. (Box 96, Folder 1)
    - General. Chapter 61. Illustrations [photocopies, captions, slides]. (Box 96, Folder 2)
    - General. Chapter 62. Illustrations [photocopies, captions, slides]. (Box 96, Folder 3)
    - General. Chapter 64. Illustrations [photocopies, captions, slides]. (Box 96, Folder 4)
    - General. Chapter 65. Illustrations [photocopies, captions, slides]. (Box 96, Folder 5)
    - General. Chapter 66. Illustrations [photocopies, captions, slides]. (Box 96, Folder 6)
    - General. Chapter 69. Illustrations [photocopies, captions, slides]. (Box 96, Folder 7)
    - General. Chapter 67. Illustrations [photocopies, captions, slides]. (Box 96, Folder 8)
    - General. Chapter 68. Illustrations [photocopies, captions, slides]. (Box 96, Folder 9)
    - General. Chapter 70. Illustrations [photocopies, captions, slides]. (Box 96, Folder 10)
    - General. Chapter 71. Illustrations [photocopies, captions, slides]. (Box 96, Folder 11)
    - General. Chapter 72. Illustrations [photocopies, captions, slides]. (Box 96, Folder 12)
    - General. Chapter 73. Illustrations [photocopies, captions, slides]. (Box 96, Folder 13)
    - General. Chapter 74. Illustrations [photocopies, captions, slides]. (Box 96, Folder 14)
    - General. Chapter 75. Illustrations [photocopies, captions, slides]. (Box 96, Folder 15)
    - General. Chapter 76. Illustrations [photocopies, captions, slides]. (Box 96, Folder 16)
    - General. Chapter 77. Illustrations [photocopies, captions, slides]. (Box 96, Folder 17)
    - General. Chapter 78. Illustrations [photocopies, captions, slides]. (Box 96, Folder 18)
    - General. Chapter 85. Illustrations [photocopies, captions, slides]. (Box 96, Folder 19)
    - General. Chapter 87. Illustrations [photocopies, captions, slides]. (Box 96, Folder 20)
    - General. Chapter 88. Illustrations [photocopies, captions, slides]. (Box 96, Folder 21)
    - General. Chapter 90. Illustrations [photocopies, captions, slides]. (Box 96, Folder 22)
    - General. Chapter 91. Illustrations [photocopies, captions, slides]. (Box 96, Folder 23)
    - General. Chapter 92. Illustrations [photocopies, captions, slides]. (Box 96, Folder 24)
    - General. Chapter 93. Illustrations [photocopies, captions, slides]. (Box 96, Folder 25)
    - General. Chapter 94. Illustrations [photocopies, captions, slides]. (Box 96, Folder 26)
    - General. Chapter 96. Illustrations [photocopies, captions, slides]. (Box 96, Folder 27)
    - General. Chapter 97. Illustrations [photocopies, captions, slides]. (Box 96, Folder 28)
    - General. Chapter 98. Illustrations [photocopies, captions, slides]. (Box 96, Folder 29)
    - General. Chapter 99 and 100. Illustrations [photocopies, captions, slides]. (Box 96, Folder 30)
    - Zimmerman, Manfred. [No chapter number]. Chapter 2A. 1985-1986. (Box 96, Folder 31)
    - Bonica, John J. Chapter 3. Illustrations. Not used. (Box 96, Folder 32)
    - Brena, Steven F. [No chapter number]. Illustration. Not using. (Box 96, Folder 33)
    - Bonica, John J. Chapter 24. Illustrations. Not used / extra. (Box 96, Folder 34)
    - Olesen, Jes. Chapter 39. Illustrations. Extra. (Box 96, Folder 35)
    - Matsen, Frederick A., III. Chapter 50. Photographs. Extra / not used. (Box 96, Folder 36)
    - Benedetti, Costantino. Chapter 78. Illustration. Not used. (Box 96, Folder 37)
    - Lee, Mathew H. M. Chapter 88. Photographs. Obsolete. (Box 96, Folder 38)
    - Loeser, John D. Chapter 97. Illustrations. Obsolete. (Box 96, Folder 39)
    - Rosomoff, Hubert L. Chapter 98. Illustrations. Extra. (Box 96, Folder 40)
    - Jannetta, Peter J. Chapter 99. Illustrations. Extra. (Box 96, Folder 41)
    - General. [No chapter number]. Page proofs. Pages i - 72. (Box 96, Folder 42)
    - General. [No chapter number]. Page proofs. Pages 73 - 234. (Box 96, Folder 43)
    - General. [No chapter number]. Page proofs. Pages 235 - 394. (Box 96, Folder 44)
    - General. [No chapter number]. Page proofs. Pages 395 - 554. (Box 96, Folder 45)
    - General. [No chapter number]. Page proofs. Pages 555 - 714, 746 - 758. (Box 96, Folder 46)
    - General. [No chapter number]. Page proofs. Pages 747 - 810, 875 - lxxv. (Box 96, Folder 47)
    - General. [No chapter number]. Page proofs. Pages i - 966, 971 - 1044, 1047 - 94. (Box 96, Folder 48)
    - General. [No chapter number]. Page proofs. Pages 1095 - 1150, 1153 - 1254. (Box 96, Folder 49)
    - General. [No chapter number]. Page proofs. Pages 1255 - 1414. (Box 96, Folder 50)
    - General. [No chapter number]. Page proofs. Pages 1415 - 1574. (Box 96, Folder 51)
    - General. [No chapter number]. Page proofs. Pages 1575 - 1734. (Box 96, Folder 52)
    - General. [No chapter number]. Page proofs. Pages 1735 - 1862, 1895 - 1958. (Box 96, Folder 53)
    - General. [No chapter number]. Page proofs. Pages 1959 - lxxv. (Box 96, Folder 54)
    - General. [No chapter number]. Lea & Febiger [correspondence], 1961-1981. (Box 96, Folder 55)
    - General. [No chapter number]. Outline of book, 1971-1974. (Box 96, Folder 56)
    - General. [No chapter number]. [Authors and format,] 1971-1974. (Box 96, Folder 57)
    - General. [No chapter number]. Lea & Febiger contract agreement, 1972. (Box 96, Folder 58)
    - General. [No chapter number]. Negative responses, 1972. (Box 96, Folder 59)
    - General. [No chapter number]. Formats for chapters, 1972. (Box 97, Folder 1)
    - General. [No chapter number]. Correspondence, 1972-1974. (Box 97, Folder 2)
    - General. [No chapter number]. Miscellaneous, 1972-1974. (Box 97, Folder 3)
    - General. [No chapter number]. Correspondence with authors, general correspondence, .and addresses, 1972-1980 (Box 97, Folder 4)
    - General. [No chapter number]. Format (chapter & manuscript), 1972-1985. (Box 97, Folder 5)
    - General. [No chapter number]. Format (chapter & manuscript), 1972-1985. (Box 97, Folder 6)
    - General. [No chapter number]. Permissions and forms, 1980. (Box 97, Folder 7)
    - General. [No chapter number]. Lea & Febiger correspondence, 1981-1987. (Box 97, Folder 8)
    - General. [No chapter number]. Proposals, 1983. (Box 97, Folder 9)
    - General. [No chapter number]. [Front matter and appendices,] 1983. (Box 97, Folder 10)
    - General. [No chapter number]. Suggestions re: second edition, 1983. (Box 97, Folder 11)
    - General. [No chapter number]. Letters to reviewers, 1983. (Box 97, Folder 12)
    - General. [No chapter number]. Negative responses to chapter requests, 1983-1985. (Box 97, Folder 13)
    - General. [No chapter number]. Correspondence, 1983-1985. (Box 97, Folder 14)
    - General. [No chapter number]. Management of Pain in Clinical Practice, 1983-1987. (Box 97, Folder 15)
    - General. [No chapter number]. Secretary working file, 1983-1987. (Box 97, Folder 16)
    - General. [No chapter number]. Table of contents, 1983-1987. (Box 97, Folder 17)
    - General. [No chapter number]. [Planning and outline,] 1983-1987. (Box 97, Folder 18)
    - General. [No chapter number]. Lea & Febiger instructions to authors, 1983-1989. (Box 97, Folder 19)
    - General. [No chapter number]. Master reference list, 1984. (Box 97, Folder 20)
    - General. [No chapter number]. Invitation letters, 1984-1985. (Box 97, Folder 21)
    - General. [No chapter number]. Colaiezzi-samples of type, 1984-1988. (Box 97, Folder 22)
    - General. [No chapter number]. Mailing lists, 1984-1990. (Box 97, Folder 23)
    - General. [No chapter number]. Journal PAIN references, 1985. (Box 97, Folder 24)
    - General. [No chapter number]. [Contents, authors,] 1985. (Box 97, Folder 25)
    - General. [No chapter number]. Correspondence, 1985-1989. (Box 97, Folder 26)
    - General. [No chapter number]. Lea & Febiger correspondence, 1987-1988. (Box 97, Folder 27)
    - General. [No chapter number]. Permission tables, 1987-1989. (Box 97, Folder 28)
    - General. [No chapter number]. Publicity, 1987-1989. (Box 97, Folder 29)
    - General. [No chapter number]. Lists of contributors (obsolete), 1987. (Box 97, Folder 30)
    - General. [No chapter number]. Bigos permission forms hold for Donna, 1988. (Box 97, Folder 31)
    - General. [No chapter number]. Lea & Febiger contract, 1988. (Box 97, Folder 32)
    - General. [No chapter number]. Correspondence with Carroll Cann, 1988-1989. (Box 97, Folder 33)
    - General. [No chapter number]. Correspondence with David Amundson, 1988-1989. (Box 97, Folder 34)
    - General. [No chapter number]. Express delivery reciepts, 1988-1990. (Box 97, Folder 35)
    - General. [No chapter number]. Final contributors, 1989. (Box 97, Folder 36)
    - General. [No chapter number]. Contributors, queries and list, 1989-1990. (Box 97, Folder 37)
    - General. [No chapter number]. Lea & Febiger correspondence, 1989-1990. (Box 97, Folder 38)
    - General. [No chapter number]. Letters re: second edition, 1990. (Box 97, Folder 39)
    - General. [No chapter number]. MOP2 reviews, 1990. (Box 97, Folder 40)
    - General. [No chapter number]. Signature pages, 1990. (Box 97, Folder 41)
    - General. [No chapter number]. Comments by authors, 1990. (Box 97, Folder 42)
    - General. [No chapter number]. Book reviews, 1990-1992. (Box 97, Folder 43)
    - General. [No chapter number]. Publicity, 1990-1991. (Box 97, Folder 44)
    - General. [No chapter number]. Lea & Febiger correspondence, 1990-1991. (Box 97, Folder 45)
    - General. [No chapter number]. MOP2 matted illustrations, chapters 1-56. (Box 98, Folder unknown container)
    - General. [No chapter number]. MOP2 matted illustrations, chapters 57-94. (Box 99, Folder unknown container)
    - General. [No chapter number]. MOP2 matted illustrations, chapters 96-100; not used, .seconds, miscellaneous (Box 100, Folder unknown container)
    - General. [No chapter number]. Matted illustrations. (Box 142, Folder unknown container)
    - General. [No chapter number]. Matted illustrations. (Box 143, Folder unknown container)
    - General. [No chapter number]. Matted illustrations. (Box 144, Folder unknown container)
    - General. [No chapter number]. Matted illustrations. (Box 146, Folder 3)
  - Principles and Practice of Obstetric Analgesia and Anesthesia, Vols. 1 and 2
    - PP of OB AA, 1st ed. Table of Contents. (Box 101, Folder 1)
    - PP of OB AA, 1st ed. Acknowledgements. 1st Foreword. (Box 101, Folder 2)
    - PP of OB AA, 1st ed. Introduction. (Box 101, Folder 3)
    - PP of OB AA, 1st ed. Chapter 1, Physiology of Pregnancy. (Box 101, Folder 4)
    - PP of OB AA, 1st ed. Chapter 1, Physiology of Pregnancy [related reprints]. (Box 101, Folder 5)
    - PP of OB AA, 1st ed. Chapter 2, Psychologic Aspects of Pregnancy, etc. (Box 101, Folder 6)
    - PP of OB AA, 1st ed. Chapter 2, Psychologic Aspects of Pregnancy, etc. [related reprints]. (Box 101, Folder 7)
    - PP of OB AA, 1st ed. Chapter 3, Physiology of Forces of Parturition. (Box 101, Folder 8)
    - PP of OB AA, 1st ed. Chapter 3, Physiology of Forces of Parturition [related reprints]. (Box 101, Folder 9)
    - PP of OB AA, 1st ed. Chapter 3, Physiology of Labor and Childbirth [related reprints]. (Box 101, Folder 10)
    - PP of OB AA, 1st ed. Chapter 4, Effects of Parturition on Mother [includes related reprints]. (Box 101, Folder 11)
    - PP of OB AA, 1st ed. Chapter 5, Nature of Pain of Parturition. (Box 101, Folder 12)
    - PP of OB AA, 1st ed. Chapter 6, Anatomy & Physiology of Placenta. (Box 101, Folder 13)
    - PP of OB AA, 1st ed. Chapter 6, Anatomy and Physiology of Placenta [related reprints]. (Box 101, Folder 14)
    - PP of OB AA, 1st ed. Chapter 7, Physilogy of Fetus and Newborn. (Box 101, Folder 15)
    - PP of OB AA, 1st ed. Chapter 7, Physiology of Fetus and Newborn [related reprints]. (Box 101, Folder 16)
    - PP of OB AA, 1st ed. Chapter 7, Physiology of Fetus and Newborn [related reprints]. (Box 101, Folder 17)
    - PP of OB AA, 1st ed. Chapter 8, Effects of Parturition on Fetus and Newborn [includes related reprints]. (Box 101, Folder 18)
    - PP of OB AA, 1st ed. Chapter 9, Placental Transfer & Effect on Fetus and Newborn. (Box 102, Folder 1)
    - PP of OB AA, 1st ed. Chapter 9, ANILERIDINE (LERITINE) [related reprints]. (Box 102, Folder 2)
    - PP of OB AA, 1st ed. Chapter 9, NEWER NARCOTICS [related reprints]. (Box 102, Folder 3)
    - PP of OB AA, 1st ed. Chapter 9, NARCOTIC ANTAGONISTS [related reprints]. (Box 102, Folder 4)
    - PP of OB AA, 1st ed. Chapter 9, DEMEROL [related reprints]. (Box 102, Folder 5)
    - PP of OB AA, 1st ed. Chapter 9, MORPHINE [related reprints]. (Box 102, Folder 6)
    - PP of OB AA, 1st ed. Chapter 10, Asphyxia Neo. & Perinatal M & M. (Box 102, Folder 7)
    - PP of OB AA, 1st ed. Chapter 10, Asphixia Neo. & Perinatal MM [related reprints]. (Box 102, Folder 8)
    - PP of OB AA, 1st ed. Chapter 11, Narcotics. (Box 102, Folder 9)
    - PP of OB AA, 1st ed. Chapter 11, Narcotics [related reprints]. (Box 102, Folder 10)
    - PP of OB AA, 1st ed. Chapter 11, ALPHAPRODINE (NISENTIL) [related reprints]. (Box 102, Folder 11)
    - PP of OB AA, 1st ed. Chapter 11, CHLORPROMAZINE [related reprints]. (Box 102, Folder 12)
    - PP of OB AA, 1st ed. Chapter 11, PROMETHAZINE [related reprints]. (Box 102, Folder 13)
    - PP of OB AA, 1st ed. Chapter 12, Sedatives, Hypnotics and Ataractics. (Box 102, Folder 14)
    - PP of OB AA, 1st ed. Chapter 12, Barbituates [related reprints]. (Box 102, Folder 15)
    - PP of OB AA, 1st ed. Chapter 13, Skeletal Muscle Relaxants [includes related reprints]. (Box 102, Folder 16)
    - PP of OB AA, 1st ed. Chapter 14, Vasoconstrictors & Vasopressors. (Box 102, Folder 17)
    - PP of OB AA, 1st ed. Chapter 14, Vasoconstrictors & Vasopressors [includes related reprints]. (Box 102, Folder 18)
    - PP of OB AA, 1st ed. Chapter 15, Oxytocics and Uterine Relaxants. (Box 102, Folder 19)
    - PP of OB AA, 1st ed. Chapter 15, Oxytocics and Uterine Relaxants [includes related reprints]. (Box 102, Folder 20)
    - PP of OB AA, 1st ed. Chapter 16, Fundamental Considerations of General Anesthesia. (Box 102, Folder 21)
    - PP of OB AA, 1st ed. Chapter 17, Techniques and Physiocochemical Aspects of Inhalation Anesthesia. (Box 102, Folder 22)
    - PP of OB AA, 1st ed. Chapter 17, Techniques and Physiocochemical Aspects of Inhalation Anesthesia [includes related reprints]. (Box 102, Folder 23)
    - PP of OB AA, 1st ed. Chapter 18, Nitrous Exide and Ethylene [includes related reprints]. (Box 102, Folder 24)
    - PP of OB AA, 1st ed. Chapter 19, Cyclopropane. (Box 102, Folder 25)
    - PP of OB AA, 1st ed. Chapter 20, Trichloroethylene [includes related reprints]. (Box 102, Folder 26)
    - PP of OB AA, 1st ed. Chapter 21, Diethyl Ether & Divinyl Ether. (Box 102, Folder 27)
    - PP of OB AA, 1st ed. Chapter 22, Halothane. (Box 102, Folder 28)
    - PP of OB AA, 1st ed. Chapter 23, Methoxyflurane [includes related reprints]. (Box 102, Folder 29)
    - PP of OB AA, 1st ed. Chapter 24, Chloroform. (Box 102, Folder 30)
    - PP of OB AA, 1st ed. Chapter 25, Fluroxene & Misc. Inhalation Anesth. (Box 102, Folder 31)
    - PP of OB AA, 1st ed. Chapter 26, Intravenous Anesthetics. (Box 102, Folder 32)
    - PP of OB AA, 1st ed. Chapter 27, Rectal Anesthesia. (Box 102, Folder 33)
    - PP of OB AA, 1st ed. Chapter 28, Balanced Analgesia & Anesthesia. (Box 102, Folder 34)
    - PP of OB AA, 1st ed. Chapter 29, Fundamental Considerations (Regional). (Box 102, Folder 35)
    - PP of OB AA, 1st ed. Chapter 30, Pudendal Block & Local Anesthesia [includes related reprints]. (Box 102, Folder 36)
    - PP of OB AA, 1st ed. Chapter 31, Paracervical & Uterosacral Block [includes related reprints]. (Box 103, Folder 1)
    - PP of OB AA, 1st ed. Chapter 32, Lumbar Sympathetic Block [includes related reprints]. (Box 103, Folder 2)
    - PP of OB AA, 1st ed. Chapter 33, Local-Regional Analg. for Abdominal. (Box 103, Folder 3)
    - PP of OB AA, 1st ed. Chapter 34, Subarachnoid Block. (Box 103, Folder 4)
    - PP of OB AA, 1st ed. Chapter 34, Subarachnoid Block [related reprints]. (Box 103, Folder 5)
    - PP of OB AA, 1st ed. Chapter 35, Caudal Block. (Box 103, Folder 6)
    - PP of OB AA, 1st ed. Chapter 35, Caudal Block [related reprints]. (Box 103, Folder 7)
    - PP of OB AA, 1st ed. Chapter 36, Spinal (Lumbar) Epidural Block [includes related reprints]. (Box 103, Folder 8)
    - PP of OB AA, 1st ed. Chapter 37, Miscellaneous Techniques. (Box 103, Folder 9)
    - PP of OB AA, 1st ed. Chapter 38, Respiratory Complications [includes related reprints]. (Box 103, Folder 10)
    - PP of OB AA, 1st ed. Chapter 39, Aspiration of Gastric Contents [includes related reprints]. (Box 103, Folder 11)
    - PP of OB AA, 1st ed. Chapter 40, Cardiovascular Complications [includes related reprints]. (Box 103, Folder 12)
    - PP of OB AA, 1st ed. Chapter 41, Neurologic Complications [includes related reprints]. (Box 103, Folder 13)
    - PP of OB AA, 1st ed. Chapter 42, Hepatic, Renal & other Complications. (Box 103, Folder 14)
    - PP of OB AA, 1st ed. Chapter 43, Maternal Mortality. (Box 103, Folder 15)
    - PP of OB AA, 1st ed. Chapter 43, Maternal Mortality [related reprints]. (Box 103, Folder 16)
    - PP of OB AA, 1st ed. Chapter 44, Principles & Techniques of Hypnosis [includes related reprints]. (Box 103, Folder 17)
    - PP of OB AA, 1st ed. Chapter 45, Principles & Technique of Natural Childbirth [includes related reprints]. (Box 103, Folder 18)
    - PP of OB AA, 1st ed. Chapter 46, Principles & Techniques of Psycoprophylactic Method. (Box 103, Folder 19)
    - PP of OB AA, 1st ed. Chapter 47, Evaluation of Psychologic Methods of Analgesia. (Box 104, Folder 1)
    - PP of OB AA, 1st ed. Introduction to Volume 2. (Box 104, Folder 2)
    - PP of OB AA, 1st ed. Chapter 48, Antepartal Management [includes related reprints]. (Box 104, Folder 3)
    - PP of OB AA, 1st ed. Chapter 49, Normal Labor. (Box 104, Folder 4)
    - PP of OB AA, 1st ed. Chapter 50, Normal Vaginal Delivery [includes related reprints]. (Box 104, Folder 5)
    - PP of OB AA, 1st ed. Chapter 51, [Management of] Newborn. (Box 104, Folder 6)
    - PP of OB AA, 1st ed. Chapter 52, Postpartum Management [of the Mother] [includes related reprints]. (Box 104, Folder 7)
    - PP of OB AA, 1st ed. Chapter 53, Heart Disease [includes related reprints]. (Box 104, Folder 8)
    - PP of OB AA, 1st ed. Chapter 54, Circulatory Disorders [includes related reprints]. (Box 104, Folder 9)
    - PP of OB AA, 1st ed. Chapter 55, Pulmonary Diseases [includes related reprints]. (Box 104, Folder 10)
    - PP of OB AA, 1st ed. Chapter 56, Anes Mgmt/Part w/ Endocrine Disorders [includes related reprints]. (Box 104, Folder 11)
    - PP of OB AA, 1st ed. Chapter 57, Diabetes [includes related reprints]. (Box 104, Folder 12)
    - PP of OB AA, 1st ed. Chapter 58, [Diseases of the] Kidney and Urinary Tract [includes related reprints]. (Box 104, Folder 13)
    - PP of OB AA, 1st ed. Chapter 59, Liver and Gastrointestinal Disorders [includes related reprints]. (Box 104, Folder 14)
    - PP of OB AA, 1st ed. Chapter 60, Hematologic Disorders. (Box 104, Folder 15)
    - PP of OB AA, 1st ed. Chapter 61, Neurologic Disorders [includes related reprints]. (Box 104, Folder 16)
    - PP of OB AA, 1st ed. Chapter 62, Psychiatric Disorders. (Box 104, Folder 17)
    - PP of OB AA, 1st ed. Chapter 63, Non-obstetric Diseases [includes related reprints]. (Box 104, Folder 18)
    - PP of OB AA, 1st ed. Chapter 64, Part w/ Toxemia. (Box 104, Folder 19)
    - PP of OB AA, 1st ed. Chapter 64, Toxemia [related reprints]. (Box 104, Folder 20)
    - PP of OB AA, 1st ed. Chapter 65, Shock [includes related reprints]. (Box 104, Folder 21)
    - PP of OB AA, 1st ed. Chapter 66, Placenta Previa, etc. [Abruptio Placentae or Rupture of the Uterus] [includes related reprints]. (Box 104, Folder 22)
    - PP of OB AA, 1st ed. Chapter 67, Dystocia [Caused by an Abnormal Passage] [includes related reprints]. (Box 105, Folder 1)
    - PP of OB AA, 1st ed. Chapter 68, Dysfunction of the Forces of Labor [includes related reprints]. (Box 105, Folder 2)
    - PP of OB AA, 1st ed. Chapter 69, Abnormal Presentations [includes related reprints]. (Box 105, Folder 3)
    - PP of OB AA, 1st ed. Chapter 70, Breech Delivery [includes related reprints]. (Box 105, Folder 4)
    - PP of OB AA, 1st ed. Chapter 71, The Grand Multipara; Other Obstetric Complications. (Box 105, Folder 5)
    - PP of OB AA, 1st ed. Chapter 72, Fetal Distress [includes related reprints]. (Box 105, Folder 6)
    - PP of OB AA, 1st ed. Chapter 73, Dysmaturity [Prematurity and Postmaturity (Including Respiratory Distress Syndrome)]. (Box 105, Folder 7)
    - PP of OB AA, 1st ed. Chapter 74, Multiple Gestations [includes related reprints]. (Box 105, Folder 8)
    - PP of OB AA, 1st ed. Chapter 75, Induction of Labor [includes related reprints]. (Box 105, Folder 9)
    - PP of OB AA, 1st ed. Chapter 76, Forceps Delivery [includes related reprints]. (Box 105, Folder 10)
    - PP of OB AA, 1st ed. Chapter 77, Cesarean Section [includes related reprints]. (Box 105, Folder 11)
    - PP of OB AA, 1st ed. Chapter 78, Other Operative Obstetric Prodedures [related reprints]. (Box 105, Folder 12)
    - PP of OB AA, 1st ed. Chapter 79, Pulmonary or Cardiovascular Surgery. (Box 105, Folder 13)
    - PP of OB AA, 1st ed. Chapter 80, Abdominal, Orthopedic and Other Surgery. (Box 105, Folder 14)
    - PP of OB AA, 1st ed. Chapter 1, Physiology of Pregnancy. Illustrations. (Box 105, Folder 15)
    - PP of OB AA, 1st ed. Chapter 1, Physiology of Pregnancy. Illustrations. (Box 105, Folder 16)
    - PP of OB AA, 1st ed. Chapter 2, Psychologic Aspects of Pregnancy. Illustrations. (Box 105, Folder 17)
    - PP of OB AA, 1st ed. Chapter 3, Physiology of Forces of Parturition. Illustrations. (Box 105, Folder 18)